KALASH **JAIN**

22051 Cleveland St., Dearborn, MI · 3132660068

Kalashjain45@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/kalash-jain-92861459 · https://github.com/Jain-Kalash

I am an aspiring Data Scientist with interest in the field of Deep Learning, Data Science, and Computer Vision. I have the working experience of Python, C, C++, and Java of 5+ years. I have developed a number of fun projects using ML, DL, NLP concepts. I am a self-motivated, self-learner who not only learns the concepts but implement them in real world projects.

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2017 - APRIL 2018

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN, PANASONIC AUTOMOTIVE SYSTEMS

Worked on Predictive Analysis for the data acquired from the Infotainment systems of automobiles and processing it for data mining, drawing patterns and predictions using Tensorflow, User Management, and Systems Engineering.

JANUARY 2017 - APRIL 2017

RESEARCH ASSISTANT, WAYNE STATE UNIVERSITY

Developed a system using Python for a visuomotor task in which subjects standing on a force platform must shift their weight to move a cursor on a screen to follow a target.

EDUCATION

APRIL 2018

MASTER OF SCIENCE- COMPUTER SCIENCE, WAYNE STATE UNIVERSITY

Recipient of Graduate Professional Scholarship (2017-18) and Dean Merit's Scholarship (2017).

APRIL 2016

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING- COMPUTER SCIENCE, RAJIV GANDHI TECHNOLOGICAL

UNIVERSITY

Recipient of Chancellor's Scholarship (2013, 2015) and Batch Valedictorian (2012-2016).

SKILLS

- Python (5+ Years), C, C++, Java (6 Years), R (2 years), Tensorflow (3 years), Hadoop, Map Reduce, Hive, Pig, HBase, Spark, Shark (3+ years).
- Classification, Regression, Clustering, Anomaly Detection, Predictive Analysis, Neural Networks, DNN, CNN, RNN.

PROJECTS

- Auto-coder: Let the Computer Code [March '18]
- Fake Job Email Filter [November '17]
- Chat-bot Machine Learning Project [January '17]
- Michigan Pollution Data-Data Mining Project [August '16]
- Language Enhancement using Adaptive Machine Learning [January '16]